NEW

[Try Grindr on the Web

](https://web.grindr.com/)

Browse bigger

No download required

Use on any device

Chat faster

[Download](https://www.grindr.com/)[About](https://www.grindr.com/about)[Help

](https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us)[Community Resources

](https://www.grindr.com/help)[Advertise](https://www.grindr.com/advertise)[Careers](https://www.grindr.com/careers)[GRINDR FOR EQUALITY](https://www.grindr.com/g4e)[Blog](https://www.grindr.com/blog)[Video

](https://www.youtube.com/grindr)[](https://shop.grindr.com/)[Unlimited](https://www.grindr.com/unlimited)[Investors

](https://investors.grindr.com/overview/default.aspx)

Follow us

©2024 Grindr LLC  

Close

Grindr Privacy and Cookie Policy
================================

English

[Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/en-us)[Personal Information We Collect And Data Retention](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/personal-information-collected-and-data-retention/en-us)[How We Share Personal Information](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/how-we-may-share/en-us)[Behavioral Advertising](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/behavioral-advertising/en-us)[Cookies and Other Tech](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/cookies-and-other-tech/en-us)[Third-Parties](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/third-parties/en-us)[Legal Bases](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/legal-bases/en-us)[Your U.S. State Privacy Rights](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/your-us-state-privacy-rights/en-us)[South Korean Privacy Rights](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/your-south-korean-privacy-rights/en-us)[EEA and UK Rep Addresses](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/eea-rep-addresses/en-us)[Privacy Rights Requests](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/privacy-rights-requests/en-us)[Grindr Employee, Contractor, Vendor and Applicant Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/applicant-privacy-policy)[Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/applicant-privacy-policy)

[Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/en-us)[Personal Information We Collect And Data Retention](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/personal-information-collected-and-data-retention/en-us)[How We Share Personal Information](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/how-we-may-share/en-us)[Behavioral Advertising](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/behavioral-advertising/en-us)[Cookies and Other Tech](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/cookies-and-other-tech/en-us)[Third-Parties](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/third-parties/en-us)[Legal Bases](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/legal-bases/en-us)[Your U.S. State Privacy Rights](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/your-us-state-privacy-rights/en-us)[South Korean Privacy Rights](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/your-south-korean-privacy-rights/en-us)[EEA and UK Rep Addresses](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/eea-rep-addresses/en-us)[Privacy Rights Requests](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/privacy-rights-requests/en-us)[Grindr Employee, Contractor, Vendor and Applicant Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/applicant-privacy-policy)[Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/consumer-health-data-privacy-policy)

<p><span>Effective Date: The earlier of 2024-12-02 or user acknowledgment.</span></p><p><span >Welcome to Grindr&#39;s Privacy and Cookie Policy (&quot;Policy&quot;). All references in this policy to &quot;Grindr&quot;, &quot;we&quot;, &quot;us&quot;, or &quot;our&quot;, refer to Grindr LLC, its parent companies, and its subsidiaries such as Grindr Canada Inc. This Policy explains how Grindr LLC processes and puts you in control of your Personal Information. At Grindr, &quot;Personal Information&quot; means any information that allows someone to identify, or reasonably link to, you directly or indirectly. When we describe &quot;processing&quot; of Personal Information, we mean how we collect, use, share, and retain Personal Information. This policy covers these activities across all of our properties (&quot;Properties&quot; or &quot;Grindr Properties&quot;). We have included </span ><span>\[LEARN MORE\]</span ><span >&nbsp;page links that describe additional details you may find helpful.</span ></p><p><span>This policy covers the following Grindr Properties:</span></p><ul><li><span>The Grindr applications and related features (the &quot;</span ><span>Grindr App</span><span>&quot; or &quot;</span><span>App</span ><span>&quot;) including web </span ><span><a href="https://web.grindr.com/">https://web.grindr.com</a></span ><span>&nbsp;(&quot;</span><span>Grindr Web</span ><span >&quot;) and mobile platforms and any related services (collectively known as the &quot;</span ><span>Grindr Services</span><span>&quot;), and</span></li><li><span>The website </span ><span><a href="https://www.grindr.com/">https://www.grindr.com</a></span ><span>&nbsp;(&quot;</span><span>Grindr Site</span><span>&quot;).</span></li></ul><p><span >For processing of Personal Information of Grindr employees, contractors, and job applicants, please click </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/applicant-privacy-policy/" >here</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;to review our related processing practices.</span></p><p><span >For processing of Consumer Health Data of Grindr users who are Washington or Nevada residents and individuals whose data is collected in Washington or Nevada, please click </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/consumer-health-data-privacy-policy" >here</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;to review our related processing practices.</span></p><p><span></span></p><p><span>Our Commitment to Privacy.</span ><span >&nbsp;As a global LGTBQ+ social networking application, the Grindr Properties allow you to share information about yourself with us, Grindr&#39;s service providers who help us provide our Properties, and other Grindr users, including your precise location and information that may be deemed &quot;sensitive&quot; or &quot;special category&quot; in certain jurisdictions such as ethnicity, information about your sex life, sexual preferences, or your self-reported health information. Our goal is to put you in control of as much of the Personal Information that you share within the Grindr Properties as possible. We recommend you read this Privacy and Cookie Policy and our </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/terms-of-service/" >Terms and Conditions of Service</a ></span ><span >&nbsp;carefully. To support our commitment to continued transparency, in addition to regular updates to this Policy, within the Grindr Services you will see occasional pop-up privacy notices meant to help you understand what you are participating in when you choose to use certain features or services.</span ></p><p><span>Grindr LLC is a U.S.-based Company.</span ><span >&nbsp;By using the Grindr Properties, you are transmitting information to Grindr in the United States and its service providers (in the United States and other third countries). If you are a resident of another country, note that the United States and other third countries may not afford the same privacy protections as your country of residence.</span ></p><p><span>Permissible Age</span ><span >. The Grindr Properties are intended only for users who are legal adults, generally eighteen (18) years of age and older. If you are aware that a child or minor has submitted Personal Information on the Grindr Properties, please contact us by either using the in-app reporting tool (click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/1500008659902-Blocking-reporting-profiles%2523h\_01FM049R9XRYZDSHJ0JS335QJB" >here</a ></span ><span >&nbsp;for more information) or by submitting a request outside of your Grindr account by clicking </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360005715154%26ticket\_form\_id%253D360005715154%2526tf%253D%3D" >here</a ></span ><span>, so that we can take appropriate action.</span></p><p><span>U.S. State Residents (as allowed under applicable laws).</span ><span>&nbsp;Please see </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/your-us-state-privacy-rights/en-us" >Your U.S. State Privacy Rights</a ></span ><span >&nbsp;to learn about the specific rights that may be afforded to you under applicable U.S. state privacy laws.</span ></p><h3><span>PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT</span></h3><p><span >When you use the Grindr Properties, we collect Personal Information about you, the majority of which you choose to provide. We may collect data about your interactions, use, and experiences with our Properties and receive information from third parties. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/third-parties/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></p><ul><li><span>Personal Information You Are Required To Provide</span ><span >. When you set up an account, we require that you provide limited Personal Information such as email or phone number and date of birth to validate that you are an adult.</span ></li><li><span>Personal Information You Have The Option To Provide.</span ><span >&nbsp;You have a choice about what Personal Information you provide as part of your public profile (&quot;Grindr Profile&quot;). Personal Information which you include in your Grindr Profile is referred to as your &quot;Profile Information&quot; and is shared with other users of the Grindr Services (the &quot;Grindr Community&quot;). For example, you may choose to share or not share location, HIV status, vaccination status, photos and videos. Note, however, that choosing not to provide certain information may impact the functionality of certain Grindr Services. You may also optionally provide Personal Information to us for feedback and customer support services or when you agree to participate in surveys. Such data varies from survey to survey.</span ><ul><li><span>Note on &quot;sensitive&quot; Personal Information.</span ><span >&nbsp;In some jurisdictions and under some regulations, information that may reveal an individual&#39;s racial or ethnic origin, details on their health or sex life/sexual orientation, or precise geolocation, among other data, may be considered &quot;sensitive&quot; or &quot;special category&quot; Personal Information.</span ></li><li><span>A note on location information.</span ><span >&nbsp;We may collect your precise location (&quot;Location&quot;) from your device to determine your distance from other users (&quot;Distance Information&quot;) and display your profile on the Grindr Properties. Sophisticated users who use the Grindr Services in an unauthorized manner, or other users who change their location while you remain in the same location, may use Distance Information to determine your exact location and may be able to determine your identity. You may choose to hide your Distance Information; however, if you continue to use the Grindr Services the Grindr Services will continue to sort and display your profile based on your relative distance from other users. Accordingly, even if you choose to hide your Distance Information, others may nevertheless be able to determine your Location. You may revoke this permission and disable the location services on your device on an iPhone by going to Settings&gt; Privacy&gt; Location Services&gt; Grindr; on an Android device by going to Settings&gt; Location&gt; Grindr&gt; Permissions&gt; Location; and on Grindr Web by adjusting your browser settings. </span></li></ul></li><li><span >Personal Information We Receive From Your Device When You Use The Grindr Properties. </span ><span >To maintain and improve the Grindr Properties, we collect Personal Information such as user activity, hardware and software information, and cookies, and leverage other technologies such as web beacons, software development kits (SDKs), local storage, and log files. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/cookies-and-other-tech/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></li><li><span>Personal Information We Receive From Third Parties</span ><span >. Grindr collects limited information from third parties. For example, we may collect Personal Information from payment processors, app usage and website tracking information partners, authentication partners (e.g., Google and Meta), machine learning partners, and our consent management platform provider(s).</span ></li></ul><h3><span>WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</span></h3><p><span >The main reason we use your Personal Information is to enable the Grindr Properties, such as providing you with core features of the Services, providing you with support, and supporting platform safety. We only process your Personal Information in accordance with specific processing purposes and, where required by law, under applicable legal bases. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/legal-bases/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></p><p><span>In general, we use your Personal Information to:</span></p><ul><li><span >Provide you with the Services associated with your Grindr account.</span ></li><li><span>Answer your inquiries and provide you with support.</span></li><li><span >Improve our Properties and support user safety within the Services (including machine learning/artificial intelligence (&ldquo;AI&rdquo;) and automated decision-making).</span ></li><li><span>Protect our interests as a company.</span></li><li><span >Allow you to enjoy and empower certain Service and Property features (including machine learning/AI training and automated decision-making processes - click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/7169085929491" >here</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;for more information).</span></li><li><span >Allow third-party ad / marketing partners to use cookies and other technologies for the purposes of serving ads to free users of the Services.</span ></li><li><span >Conduct surveys or obtain your voluntary feedback about our Properties.</span ></li><li><span >Respond to legal requests from law enforcement agencies, regulators, and other third-parties to comply with &quot;Legal Obligations&quot; (as defined below).</span ></li></ul><h3><span>OUR CONNECTION ALGORITHMS</span></h3><p><span >Grindr is committed to helping you make connections. Since 2009, Grindr has prioritized proximity to help you efficiently find users closest to you. Going forward we want to help you find the best connections for you whether that is based on how close your match is to you or that your perfect connection also shares an interest in drag brunch. Therefore, we may use different indicators from your profile and in-app interactions to recommend relevant profiles to you in order to help maximize your chance of making a meaningful Grindr connection. Our algorithms are based on a range of factors and prioritize your interests all while attempting to reduce bias. We may use the following data about you and others in the Grindr Community to make recommendations for you: </span ><span>the Personal Information You Have The Option To Provide </span ><span >such as your tags, age, and gender so we can show you people with similar interests;</span ><span >&nbsp;Personal Information We Receive From Your Device When You Use The Grindr Properties</span ><span >&nbsp;such as user profiles you have viewed to understand your preferences;</span ><span>&nbsp;and Personal Information We Receive From Third Parties</span ><span >&nbsp;such as your location in order to show you people closest to you</span ><span>. </span><span>You can view our </span><span>Legal Bases</span ><span >&nbsp;section to understand our grounds for processing such information. Please know, you still remain in control of what information you include in your profile, and where you have chosen to disclose sensitive or special category information, we rely upon your consent to use such information. </span></p><h3><span>HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</span></h3><p><span >To enable you to make meaningful connections, Grindr allows you to share information about yourself with the Grindr Community and third-parties in connection with our providing you with the Grindr Properties as described in this Policy. In general, we share your Personal Information in the following ways:</span ></p><ul><li><span>The Grindr Community.</span ><span >&nbsp;The Grindr Services are intended to be a safe space where you can discover, navigate, and interact with others in the Grindr Community. As part of the Services, Grindr enables you to share your Profile Information, location, and other information with the Grindr Community.</span ></li><li><span>Third-Party Partners.</span ><span >&nbsp;Grindr shares Personal Information with a number of third-party partners to bring you the Grindr Properties, such as Service Providers (e.g., Sift for fraud prevention and PartnerHero for customer support), Ad / Marketing Partners help facilitate advertising experiences (e.g., AppLovin), and Other Partners that support the Grindr Properties and with whom you may provide Personal Information to directly (e.g., Stripe for payment processing). For the avoidance of doubt, Grindr only shares HIV status, Last Tested Date, and vaccination status with necessary Service Providers such as companies that host data on our behalf (i.e., Amazon Web Services) or help in processing data access requests you initiate ( i.e., PartnerHero) - we do not share this information with any advertising companies. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/how-we-may-share/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></li><li><span>Business Transactions.</span ><span >&nbsp;If another company acquires, or plans to acquire, our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Policy.</span ></li><li><span>Legal Obligations.</span ><span >&nbsp;We may access, preserve, and disclose Personal Information to investigate, prevent, or take action in connection with: (i) enforcement of the Grindr </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/terms-of-service/" >Terms and Conditions of Service</a ></span ><span >; (ii) claims that any content or behavior violates our policies or the rights of third parties; (iii) requests for customer service; (iv) technical issues; (v) protecting the rights, property, or personal safety of Grindr; its users; or the public; (vi) lawful legal requests including subpoenas, warrants, or court orders or in connection with any legal process; (vii) establishing or exercising our legal rights or defending against legal claims; (viii) tax and accounting purposes; or (ix) as otherwise required by law, collectively &quot;Legal Obligations&quot;.</span ></li></ul><h3><span>HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</span></h3><p><span >We retain your Personal Information for no longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected or as otherwise permitted or pursuant to Legal Obligations or pursuant to the Grindr </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/terms-of-service/" >Terms and Conditions of Service</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;and/or the Grindr </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/community-guidelines/" >Community Guidelines</a ></span ><span >. We also retain a device identifier (i.e., IDFV and Android ID) and limited log information for up to a period of two years following account deletion to support internal reporting, metrics and statistics. Personal Information may be retained for longer periods of time if required for legal or security purposes. For example, Grindr may retain some account information, a device identifier (i.e., IDFV and Android ID), and limited log information for accounts that have been banned or that violate the Grindr </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/terms-of-service/" >Terms and Conditions of Service</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;and/or Grindr </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/community-guidelines/" >Community Guidelines</a ></span ><span >. In some circumstances, Grindr may also retain chat messages used for reporting violative behavior resulting in an account&#39;s ban. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/personal-information-collected-and-data-retention/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></p><p><span>Server-side and Local Storage</span ><span >: Grindr retains Personal Information on its servers to support the use of the Grindr Services, including enhanced safety features and an improved user experience across multiple platforms and devices. &nbsp;If you request your personal information to be deleted, Grindr will delete your chat messages from its systems as a part of your data erasure request in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Grindr cannot guarantee that copies of your chats are not retained on recipient&rsquo;s devices (e.g., screenshots, local cache) even after the information has been removed from Grindr&rsquo;s systems.</span ></p><h3><span>YOUR CHOICES AND RIGHTS</span></h3><p><span >Where your jurisdiction&#39;s law allows, you can make the following choices and exercise your rights regarding your Personal Information held by Grindr:</span ></p><ul><li><span>Access & Portability</span><span >&nbsp;You may request that we provide you with confirmation of the Personal Information we process and that we provide you with a machine-readable copy of your Personal Information&ndash; including the categories of such Personal Information. We may not be able to provide some elements of information if that information would also reveal Personal Information about another person or if we are legally prevented from disclosing such information. For more information on how to download your Personal Information from Grindr, click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/1500005257961-Accessing-your-personal-data" >here</a ></span ><span>. If you have questions regarding your Access reach out to us </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360006692913" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></li><li><span>Purposes for Processing. </span ><span >You can learn about the purposes upon which we rely for processing your Personal Information by clicking</span ><span>&nbsp;</span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/legal-bases/en-us" >here</a ></span ><span>. </span></li><li><span>Delete Account and Related Information.</span ><span >&nbsp;You may delete your account and related Profile Information at any time. After deletion, your Personal Information will be deleted from Grindr&#39;s systems in accordance with this Policy. There are circumstances where some or all of your information may be retained after your request (such as for Legal Obligations, moderation review, dispute resolution, and other matters in accordance with this Policy). For more information on how to delete your account, click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/1500008669141" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></li><li><span>Correct Profile Information.</span ><span >&nbsp;By creating an account, you are providing us your Personal Information for your Grindr Profile. You can review and change your Profile Information at any time by accessing the &quot;Edit Profile&quot; section of the Grindr Services.</span ></li><li><span >Behavioral Advertising On Websites, Third-Party Platforms, and the Grindr Services.</span ><span >&nbsp;You can opt-out of the sharing of your Personal Information (or the &quot;sale&quot; of your Personal Information as the practice may be referred to in some jurisdictions) with our Ad / Marketing Partners for behavioral advertising purposes. Please note that opting-out of behavioral advertising does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using the free version of Grindr Services. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising as provided by the applicable choice mechanisms. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/behavioral-advertising/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ><span >&nbsp;For more information on how to opt out of behavioral advertising on the various Grindr Properties, click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/12326669826323-Opt-Out-of-Behavioral-Advertising" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></li><li><span>Promotional Emails.</span ><span >&nbsp;You may choose to allow us to use your email address to send free newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to Grindr and/or the Grindr Properties, as well as targeted offers from third parties. You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in emails that you receive. If you unsubscribe from receiving such promotional emails, we may still send you service-related communications, and the Grindr Services will continue to deliver you in-app messages.</span ></li><li><span>Third-Party Tracking.</span ><span >&nbsp;In addition to controlling your preferences via our Consent Management Platform</span ><span>&nbsp;</span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/behavioral-advertising/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ><span >, you may opt-out of Google Analytics&#39; collection and use of your Personal Information on the Grindr Site by following the instructions </span ><span><a href="https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout">here</a></span ><span>&nbsp;to download an opt-out browser add-on.</span></li><li><span>Third-Party Sharing. </span ><span >You can see the Personal Information shared with third parties (including our ad/marketing partners) and the categories of third parties with whom we partner by clicking </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/how-we-may-share/en-us" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></li><li><span>Restrict Processing.</span ><span >&nbsp;Under certain circumstances, you may limit the way we process your Personal Information (e.g., through controls provided by your device&#39;s operating system, like &quot;Location&quot; (defined below) access, Location granularity, and opting out of the use of your Ad ID for behavioral advertising).</span ></li><li><span>Withdraw Consent.</span ><span >&nbsp;You may withdraw consent that you have previously given us at any time. Revocation of your consent will only apply to future processing activities and will not apply retroactively. To learn more about the processing activities where Grindr relies on your consent, refer to our Legal Bases. </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/legal-bases/en-us" >\[LEARN MORE\]</a ></span ></li><li><span>Object to Processing.</span ><span >&nbsp;You may object to us relying on our legitimate interests as the reason for why we process your Personal Information.</span ></li><li><span>Non-Discrimination.</span ><span >&nbsp;You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination. </span></li><li><span>Profiling.</span ><span >&nbsp;Your Personal Information will not involve processing for the purposes of profiling (i.e., automated decisions or inferences) in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. Grindr simply helps you make connections with other Grindr users we think you may like; we do not make decisions on employment, credit, housing, etc. &nbsp;Click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/articles/7169085929491" >here</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;for more information about Profiling. &nbsp;</span></li><li><span>Verification of Account Ownership.</span ><span >&nbsp;The easiest way to exercise your rights while protecting your privacy and security is by logging into your account to validate that you are the owner of the Grindr account. You can also make a request outside of your Grindr account by clicking&nbsp;</span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360006692913" >here</a ></span ><span >, but then we&#39;ll require some additional information to authenticate your identity associated with &nbsp;your account.</span ></li></ul><p><span >You can visit our Privacy and Safety Center within the settings menu in the App or, on the web </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/sections/4402729693971-Privacy" >here</a ></span ><span >, to learn more about our features that support your privacy and choices. To exercise your choice and rights or to make a request outside of your Grindr account, click </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360006692913" >here</a ></span ><span >. Statistics pertaining to Grindr&#39;s processing of access, erasure and opt-out requests can be found </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/privacy-rights-requests/en-us" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></p><h3><span>HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</span></h3><p><span >At Grindr, we take the privacy and security of your Personal Information, including information considered sensitive, seriously. Our cybersecurity team actively works to maintain the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of the Grindr Properties, and our policies and protocols are focused on protecting your Personal and sensitive Personal Information. We consistently strive to improve our defenses in the ongoing battle against threat actors. That said, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure, and Grindr cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. Our security, safety, and privacy features are provided on an &quot;as-is&quot; basis. As such, their effectiveness and error-free operation cannot be guaranteed, and we cannot ensure absolute confidentiality, anonymity, or personal safety. Individuals who have specific concerns about how their data may be protected are advised not to use the Properties. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of any unauthorized access to your Personal Information, we may notify you electronically or in writing in accordance with applicable law.</span ></p><h3><span>HOW TO CONTACT US OR FILE COMPLAINTS</span></h3><p><span>Contact Information.</span ><span >&nbsp;Grindr welcomes your comments, questions, or complaints regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy, our use of your Personal Information, or our response to your requests regarding your Personal Information. Please contact us by email at </span ><span>[\[email protected\]](https://www.grindr.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)</span ><span >&nbsp;or by postal mail at: Grindr LLC, Attn: Privacy Office, PO Box 69176, West Hollywood, CA 90069.</span ></p><p><span>Contact our DPOs and EEA Representative.</span ><span >&nbsp;Individuals in the European Economic Area (EEA) and the United Kingdom (UK) also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in the EEA country where they reside or work, or where the alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (&quot;GDPR&quot;) took place. You can find information about your data protection regulator </span ><span ><a href="https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en">here</a></span ><span >. Individuals in Switzerland also have the right to lodge a complaint with the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner. For complaints from individuals in the EEA, UK, or Switzerland that cannot be resolved with Grindr directly, Grindr will cooperate with EEA, UK, and Swiss authorities in order to resolve the complaints.</span ></p><p><span >If you are based in the EEA or UK or have GDPR-related inquiries, you may contact our EEA and UK Representative by submitting your request or inquiry to the postal address listed </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/eea-rep-addresses/" >here</a ></span ><span>&nbsp;for your country of residence. You may also email </span ><span>[\[email protected\]](https://www.grindr.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)</span><span>&nbsp;or submit an online form at</span ><span><a href="http://www.datarep.com/data-request">&nbsp;</a></span ><span ><a href="http://www.datarep.com/data-request" >www.datarep.com/data-request</a ></span ><span >. Please ensure your request is addressed to DataRep and not Grindr LLC. Please do not use this for general support inquiries. General support inquiries can be submitted </span ><span><a href="https://www.grindr.com/contact/">here</a></span ><span>&nbsp;or via the support link within the App. </span></p><p><span >You can also submit a request to contact Grindr&#39;s EEA and UK DPO through our website </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360006692913%26tf\_360056453953%3Dform\_\_privacy\_request\_\_eea\_dpo" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></p><p><span >If you are based in Brazil or have inquiries related to the Lei Geral de Prote&ccedil;&atilde;o de Dados Pessoais (LGPD) 13.709/2018, you may contact Grindr&#39;s Brazil DPO through our website </span ><span ><a href="https://help.grindr.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket\_form\_id%3D360006692913%26tf\_360056453953%3Dform\_\_privacy\_request\_\_brazil\_dpo" >here</a ></span ><span>.</span></p><p><span >Where necessary, we may request specific information from you to verify your identity prior to processing your request.</span ></p><h3><span>POLICY CHANGES</span></h3><p><span>The latest version of the policy available at </span ><span ><a href="https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/" >https://www.grindr.com/privacy-policy/</a ></span ><span >&nbsp;will govern our use of your Personal Information. Grindr may revise this policy from time to time. If Grindr determines, in its sole discretion, that the changes we make to this policy are material, we will notify you in advance (e.g., within the Services).</span ></p>

‍

[

Download](https://www.grindr.com/)[

About](https://www.grindr.com/about)[

Help](https://help.grindr.com/)

Menu
